How the hell
did he get to
be head coach
of the Knights?
That Knights
used to be
the bottom
of the league.
Now they're on a
winning streak,
made it all the way
to the semifinals.
Looks like Ted's
the reason.
When he was around,
we never struggled
this much to win.
So someone
that fumbles
as much as you,
James, you have a
pretty tight grip
on Ted's dick.
Those wins had
nothing to do with him.
He got a few
tricks from me.
Now he thinks
he's some genius
fucking coach.
Please.
Beating him
will be easy.
If you can't even win
against that loser,
every swinging
dick here
can pack their bags.
Coach, maybe we
should bring Ted back.
With him around,
we might actually win
the championship.
Don't you want one?
Yeah.
You all want Ted back?
Yeah, you all want
one fucking big orgy
with fucking Ted.
Okay.
Since you want your
boyfriend back,
I guess
I can't risk him
leaking my playbook.
Fine.
I'll bring him back.
Mr. Vincent,
you're about to
face the Eagles.
Do you really think
the Knights can win?
No, I, uh...
I believe in
my team.
As long as we stick
to my game plan,
the Eagles do not
stand a chance.
But from
what I've heard,
you're just a fired
assistant coach.
What makes
you so confident?
Confident in what?
His own delusions?
This guy's a clown
who loves to talk big.